Coarse coding is just like Tile coding,
Coarse Coding 和 Tile Coding 很像
but uses a sparser set of features to encode the state space.
但是使用一组更稀疏的特征来表示状态空间
Imagine dropping a bunch of circles on your 2D continuous state space.
想象一下在二维连续状态空间上放下一堆圆圈
Take any state S which is a position in this space,
选择任何一个状态 S 即在该空间中的位置
and mark all the circles that it belongs to.
并标记它所属的所有圆圈
Prepare a bit vector with a one for those circles and 0 for the rest.
构建一个位向量 这些圆圈用 1 表示 剩余圆圈用 0 表示
And that's your sparse coding representation of the state.
这就是状态的稀疏编码表示法
Looking at a 2D space helps us visualize the basic idea.
研究二维空间可以帮助我们直观地感受基本概念
But it also extends to higher dimensions where circles become spheres and hyper spheres.
但是它也可以扩展到更高维度的空间 圆圈变成球面和超球面
There are some neat properties of coarse coding.
Coarse Coding 具有一些特性
Using smaller circles results in less generalization across the space.
圆圈越小 空间的泛化程度越低
The learning algorithm has to work a bit longer,
学习算法需要持续更长时间
but you have greater effective resolution.
但是可以获得更有效的分辨率
Larger circles lead to more generalization,
圆圈越大 泛化程度越高
and in general a smoother value function.
通常会形成更平缓的值函数
You can use fewer large circles to cover the space,
你可以使用更少的大圆圈来涵盖空间
thus reducing your representation,
从而缩小表示法
but you would lose some resolution.
但是可能会失去一定的分辨率
It's not just the size of these circles that we can vary.
我们不仅可以更改这些圆圈的大小
We can change them in other ways like making them taller or
还可以从其他方面更改它们 例如更高或更宽
wider to get more resolution along one dimension versus the other.
以便在一个维度里获得更高的分辨率
In fact, this same technique generalizes to pretty much any shape.
实际上 这种技巧可以泛化到几乎任何形状
In coarse coding, just like in tile coding,
和在 Tile Coding 中一样
are resulting state representation is a binary vector.
Coarse Coding 形成的状态表示法是二元向量
Think of each tile or circle as a feature.
将每个拼贴或圆圈看做一个特征
One, if it is an active,
如果是活跃状态 则用 1 表示
zero if it is not.
否则用 0 表示
A natural extension to this idea is to use the distance
一个比较自然的扩展方法是
from the center of each circle as a measure of how active that feature is.
根据到每个圆圈中心的距离衡量该特征的活跃程度
This measure or response can be made to fall off smoothly
可以使用高斯或钟形曲线
using a Gaussian or a bell-shaped curve centered on the circle,
使这种衡量方法或响应更加平缓 曲线在圆圈上居中
which is known as a radial basis function.
称之为径向基函数
Of course, the resulting feature values will no longer be
当然 形成的特征值不再离散化
discrete so we'll end up with yet another continuous state vector.
因此又是另一个连续状态向量
But what is cool is that the number of features can be drastically reduced this way.
但是比较酷的是可以显著降低特征数量
We'll look at RBFs more closely later when we discuss function approximations.
稍后 当我们讨论函数逼近时 将详细介绍 RBF